a. How much is the t -shirt?
听音选图，根据听到的句子内容选择正确的图片。每小题读两遍。
No. 1 How much is -shirt?
No. There is an English book on the desk.
No. 2 There is an English book on the
No. Sam practices playing ping pong on weekends.
No. 3 Sam practices playing ping pong on weekends.
No. Strawberries are my favorites.
No. 4 Strawberries are my favorites.
No. Look, the bus is coming.
No. 5 Look, the bus is coming.
b. No. Excuse me, where is the nearest bookstore?
情景反应，听句子，选择正确的应答。每小题读两遍。
No. 6 Excuse me, where is the nearest bookstore?
No. Let's make a fruit salad together.
No. 7 Let's make a fruit salad together.
No. Nancy, would you like something to eat?
No. 8 Nancy, would you like something to eat?
No. I'm going to visit the science museum.
No. What were you doing at 9 o last night?
No. were you doing at 9 o last night?
c. No. It's a sunny day today, isn't it?
对话理解，听对话及问题，选择正确的答案。每组对话读两遍。
Yes, it is.
I really enjoy the sunshine.
How's the weather today?
It's a sunny day today, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I really enjoy the sunshine.
Question How's the weather today?
No. What did you do yesterday, Frank?
I went to see a friend in hospital.
He hurt his leg.
Question Where did Frank go yesterday?
What did you do yesterday, Frank?
I went to see a friend in hospital.
He hurt his leg.
Question Where did Frank go yesterday?
No. I like rock music.
How about you, Tom?
I don't like it.
I like pop music best.
Question What kind of music does Tom like best?
I like rock music.
How about you, Tom?
I don't like it.
I like pop music best.
Question What kind of music does Tom like best?
don't like it.
like music best.
No. Scott, what about going to a concert tonight?
Sorry, I can't.
I will prepare for a speech.
Question What will Scott do tonight?
Scott, what about going to a concert tonight?
Sorry, I can't.
I will prepare for a speech.
Question What will Scott do tonight?
Question 15 Rick, did you get to Shanghai by plane?
No, I went there by train.
Question How did Rick get to Shanghai?
Rick, did you get to Shanghai by plane?
No, I went there by train.
Question How did Rick get to Shanghai?
短文理解，听短文，选择正确的答案。
the Family doctor in the morning.
短文读。两遍。
Doctor, I want to know whether my wife's going deaf.
The doctor answered, here's something you can test your hearing.
Stand some meters away from her and ask her a question.
If she doesn't answer, move a little closer and ask again.
Keep saying it until she answers.
Then you will be able to know whether she is deaf or not.
The man went home and began to test his wife's hearing in the evening.
He stood by the wall and said, my dear, what's for dinner?
He didn't hear an answer.
Then he moved closer to her, my dear, what's for dinner?
Still no answer.
He said this several times until he was standing just a few feet away from her.
At last his wife answered, for the eleventh time, I say we will have meat and rice
for dinner. A man was talking to his family doctor in the morning.
I want to know whether my wife's going deaf.
The doctor answered, here's something you can test her hearing.
Stand some meters away from her and ask her a question.
If she doesn't answer, move a little closer and ask again.
Keep saying it until she answers.
Then you will be able to know whether she is deaf or not.
The man went home and began to test his wife's hearing in the evening.
He stood by the wall and said, my dear, what's for dinner?
He didn't hear an answer.
Then he moved closer to her, my dear, what's for dinner?
Still no answer.
He said this several times until he was standing just a few feet away from her.
At last his wife answered, for the eleventh time, I say we will have meat and rice
for dinner.